<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Eres mi tipo</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Configuración</string>
    <string name="action_about">Acerca de</string>
    <string name="action_profile">Perfil</string>
    <string name="action_map">Mapa</string>
    <string name="action_info">Información</string>
    <string name="first_name_prompt">Name:</string>
    <string name="about">Acerca de</string>
    <string name="logout">Cerrar sesión</string>
    <string name="shopping_cart">Shopping Cart</string>
    <string name="about_headline">Company History</string>
    <string name="about_text">In 2006, H+ Sport founder Henry Twill set out to create supplements and nutritional products made from the purest ingredients and backed by scientific and performance data – to provide a strong basis of trust and accountability. His quest began while training for his first 5K marathon, after recovering from a lengthy injury that left him with residual aches, pains, and decreased athletic performance. He was disheartened by the vast array of supplements and nutritional products on the market that subsisted of lofty claims, and little proof of those claims. He yearned for simple and natural ingredients, in their purest form, instead of labels with lengthy chemical names and disclaimers. He also cared immensely for the environment, and wanted to find products that were responsibly sourced. When no products lived up to his strict requirements, Henry set his sights on creating products that catered to his own vision. Today that vision has become H+ Sport…offering a variety of supplements, energy bars, rehydration solutions, and active wear that complement active lifestyles. At the foundation of H+ Sports are products backed by scientific and performance data, that have been created using natural and renewable resources. H+ Sport is dedicated to creating eco-friendly, high-quality, nutrient-rich, nutritional products that enhance active lifestyles. In addition, our H+ Sport Active clothing line is made to be functional, stylish, comfortable, and durable, using all natural and organic fibers.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">Acerca de</string>
    <string name="title_activity_arequirements">Requisitos</string>
    <string name="section_requirements_format">Para donar necesitas: %1$d</string>
    <string name="reqDescription1">Tener entre 18 y 65 años</string>
    <string name="reqDescription2">Identificación oficial reciente con fotografía</string>
    <string name="reqDescription3">Hacer ayuno mayor a 4 hrs y menor a 12 hrs</string>
    <string name="title_activity_informacion">Información</string>
    <string name="title_activity_nac_test">Fecha de nacimiento</string>
    <string name="title_activity_nacimiento_test">Fecha de nacimiento</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello Blank Fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_info">Información</string>
    <string name="title_activity_requirements">Requisitos</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Busca tu centro más cercano</string>
    <string name="title_activity_info_restrictions">Restricciones</string>
    <string name="title_activity_info_benefits">Información adicional</string>
    <string name="Requisitos_title">Para donar necesitas</string>
    <string name="Requisitos_body_1">Tener entre 18 y 65 años</string>
    <string name="Res_title">No dones</string>
    <string name="Requisitos_body_2">Identificación oficial reciente con fotografía</string>
    <string name="Requisitos_body_3">Hacer ayuno mayor a 4 horas y menor a 12</string>
    <string name="Requisitos_body_4">Beber mucha agua</string>
    <string name="Requisitos_body_5">Que tu último alimento no sea grasoso o contenga lácteos</string>
    <string name="Requisitos_body_6">Pesar más de 50 kilos</string>
    <string name="Restricciones_body_2">Si tomaste en las últimas 48 horas</string>
    <string name="Restricciones_body_1">Si tomaste aspirinas las últimas 72 horas o algún otro medicamento</string>
    <string name="Restricciones_body_3">Si estás embarazada</string>
    <string name="Restricciones_body_4">Si tuviste enfermedades severas del corazón, en la sangre, paludismo, epilepsia o cáncer</string>
    <string name="Restricciones_body_5">Si has tenido alguna enfermedad de transmisión sexual</string>
    <string name="Restricciones_body_6">Si te realizaste tatuaje, acupuntura, piercings, o perforaciones</string>
    <string name="Restricciones_body_7">Si estás enfermo de gripa</string>
    <string name="Ben_title">Beneficios</string>
    <string name="Beneficios_body_1">Al donar recibes un análisis completo de sangre gratis</string>
    <string name="Beneficios_body_2">Puedes llegar a salvar hasta tres vidas incluyendo la tuya</string>
    <string name="Beneficios_body_3">Puedes donar hasta 4 veces en un año o 3 si eres mujer</string>
    <string name="Beneficios_body_5">Toda tu información es confidencial</string>
    <string name="Beneficios_body_6">No genera incremento ni disminución de peso</string>
    <string name="Beneficios_body_7">La donación no acorta la vista</string>
    <string name="Beneficios_body_8">La donación no disminuye las defensas</string>
    <string name="Beneficios_body_9">No hay riesgo de infección porque los materiales son nuevos y desechables</string>
    <string name="Beneficios_body_4">Tu cuerpo recupera la sangre después de 2 meses puedes donar de nuevo</string>
    <string name="proc_body_1">Nos aseguramos de que no tengas anemia o alguna otra infección</string>
    <string name="proc_body_2">Obtener el nombre completo del paciente a quien vas a donar y en qué hospital se encuentra</string>
    <string name="proc_titulo">Proceso</string>
    <string name="proc_body_3">Tomar 450 +- 10ml de sangre con equipo estéril y desechable</string>
    <string name="proc_body_4">En este punto debes comunicar cualquier molestia para ser atendido oportunamente</string>
    <string name="proc_body_5">Después de donar permanecerás en reposo y se te dará un refrigerio</string>
    <string name="title_activity_info_proceso">Proceso</string>
    <string name="title_activity_new_map">Encuentra tu centro</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Test</string>
    <string name="title_activity_test_activity_n">Test</string>
    <string name="title_activity_register_user">Nuevo registro</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_registro">Registro</string>
    <string name="privacy_link">Aviso de privacidad</string>
    <string name="loading">Cargando...</string>
    <string name="edit_profile_button">cambiar datos</string>
    <string name="save_changes">Guardar cambios</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Olvidé contraseña</string>
    <string name="title_activity_recovery">Recuperación de contraseña</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_recovery_email">Correo de recuperación</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password (optional)</string>
    <string name="action_recovery">Recuperar contraseña</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_calis_login">Fuck it</string>
</resources>
